thaivisa.com 2013-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Thaivisa

Our Privacy Policy

  * We will never sell, share, or trade any personal or email information you provide.
  * We hold your information to be extremely confidential and completely respect your privacy.
  * You can remove your name from our newsletter at any time.

Here at Thaivisa.com we are aware of how people’s e-mail addresses can be stolen. It happens to all of us every day. Reams and reams of unsolicited mail appear in our mailbox, sent from companies that claim we have “subscribed” to their service by some action we had no idea occured.

That’s why we promise not to share your e-mail address with any other company. We are not going to sell, trade or barter your e-mail address, or ANY personal information that you may pass on to us, and we are not going to pass on third party mail at ANY time to you. Ever.

It’s a promise, and a guarantee.

**PRIVACY**

Your privacy is important to us, and we respect the privacy of all our visitors, members and clients. Any known information is kept strictly confidential. No information is ever sold or knowingly given out to any third party.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Public areas of this site do not currently use cookies. Private areas of this site may use non-persistent cookies to track the user and maintain the session.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

The use of cookies is a common practice on many website’s. For example, if you allow a website to remember your login name or password, the website places a cookie on your computer. Cookies cannot read any other information on your hard drive. We may place cookies on your computer to allow us to identify you. We may use cookies to measure web traffic, to offer you certain services, and to customize your visit. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies or would like to be notified when a website is placing a cookie on your system, your Internet browser may allow you to do so.

If you refuse cookies you might not be able to access all parts of this website.

**Web beacons**

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. These are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

If you would like to find out more about this or have any questions please contact us.

Do you have questions? [Visit our forum](http://www.thaivisa.com/forum/forum/1-thai-visas-residency-and-work-permits/)
